Narancia, when you get a
sec, let me see that key.
Look for the turtle at the water
fountain, and use this key.
Did you really...?
The thankful death!
Just the driver.
Everyone else is gone.
Yes!
It looks like they took the bait!
How'd this frickin'
hook get under my skin?
This can't be the guy that's
trying to age us to death!
Thank you.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Temasita, Junior!
Fighting God!
Yo, big bro!
Where are you?
Come on, cut it out!
I know Bucciarati and his
goons are on the train, but...
Who the hell is tugging on my hook?
No way it could be that girl Trish!
No teenage girl has that much power.
Well, whoever they are, they're a
human being that weighs 68 kilograms.
Time to reel this sucker in.
What's with this hook?
It's getting deeper.
Could this be the enemy's stand ability?
It's so quick.
It's chewing up my arm
like a damn missile.
I can't break the line.
Ooh, looks like I snagged Mista.
I definitely felt a bullet hit my line.
And the asshole with
the gun is Guido Mista.
Well played, Quick Draw, but
my line is indestructible.
Now where will the reverberation
from the bullet go?
Let's reel you in and give it a look.
I've gotta rip this thing out and fast.
I gotta do something, this thing
is gonna furrow into my brain!
Get out!
You're on, six bullets!
Pull this damn hook out of me!
Look, he's not here taking us for a ride!
It has more pulled than the
three of us put together!
Damn, seriously?
I guess I'm on my own here.
So it's time for some surgery!
Yeah!
Count on us!
We gotta track it down!
Failure is not an option,
so keep your eyes peeled!
Huh?
What was that?
Did Mista fire off his revolver?
Who the hell are you
even shooting at, huh?
What, you trying to take out
one of these poor passengers?
I get what you're trying to do, using your
bullets to ferret me out like a sniper.
Whatever, you're still screwed!
Hope you enjoyed your hearing,
because my hook is headed
straight for your inner ear!
Ah!
What are you guys doing?
You gotta aim closer or else we're never
gonna blast the ice out of this room!
It's just a little lure!
You're almost there!
Keep it moving, guys!
Blast that ice, the King of Khan!
The primary target is getting ahead now!
Go, ragazzi!
Shatter it to pieces!
What are you doing?
Of course he would be
trying to keep himself cool.
Talk about having a one-trek mind.
Damn it! You idiot!
Now you've gone and done it!
Was this guy supposed to
be the Pasty Pineapple?
Is this weird looking doobard guy?
It's him!
He's the guy that was
controlling that freaky hook!
Look, that fishing rod looking
thing must be his stand!
If I don't get some ice, Fro's age
accelerator's gonna kill me too!
Please, you have to help me! Get off!
I'm serious, geyser!
Get your rotten meds off of me!
I feel so heavy, and all I
want to do is take a good nap.
I ordered a big juicy snake, too, and now
I don't even have the energy to enjoy it!
Get the prick away, you freak!
We did it!
His hand is toast!
Get me staying here right now!
Mista, you're clear!
Hey, Mista, come on!
The stand user's ready for you!
Alright now, six bullets.
Time for you all to get
back to your stations.
I have one simple question for you.
You can ignore it if you want, but I'm
still going to ask, so just deal with it.
But I think there's something
you should know first.
If you can't find the words to muster up
a coherent response within two seconds,
I'm going to shoot hot
lead into those beady
targets framing that bugly nose of yours.
It's uno, then due.
After that, it's bye-bye, pasty.
If we're clear, I expect an honest answer.
Where the hell is your
life-stealing companion hiding out?
Ooh, no.
I don't know, man.
I've been here wondering the same thing.
And do it.
Now die, Katsune.
Please, I need your help, sir.
Oh, juicy marbled steak
used to be my favorite meal.
Would you get out of the way?
You'll be chowing down on your
steak again before you know it.
No, I don't think I will.
Oh boy, instead I'll be bringing
about your demise. What?
Who the hell are you?
End his life, thankful death.
What?
How are you?
Wait, you're not really an
old man at all, are you?
You're a death geyser.
Death comes quicker using direct contact.
Once thankful death caresses you,
your body is filled with its
soul-sucking necrotic energy.
My bullets are dying.
It's happening so fast.
Shit.
Are you really my big bro
under that saggy skin?
Whoa that's so crazy you
had me completely fooled!
You were really something bro
man attacking your own body in
order to blend in with the of the
other passengers takes real guts.
It is you!
I mean, I knew it was, but wow!
You never failed to impress, big bro.
You absolute waste of space!
What the hell was that
atrocious display back there?
How was I supposed to know the
guy was gonna shoot the ice?
There was nothing I
could do, bro, I swear!
You still don't get it, do you?
You're a goddamn Mamoni!
Not in the face, bro! Please! Have mercy!
Pesci, do you want to
know why I'm pissed off?
It's because you've been
cursed with such a weak spirit.
The beanie-wearing bastard blasted
your ice, which threw you for a loop.
Fine, it happens.
I'm also being aged, so this ain't
a walk in the park for me either.
That said, no one else from the team
would have stopped their attack.
Calling back your stand
at the moment of truth
with the enemy is the very
definition of cowardice,
little brother.
No one else would have done so even
if they were being dismembered.
So like I said, you're a damn Mamoni.
You practically pissed yourself
in that battle with Nista.
And it wasn't about the ice.
Deep down in your heart of
hearts, terror took hold of you.
You need to man up now, Pesci.
If you don't, glory will be
forever beyond our reach.
Bucciarati and his sidekicks will win.
If you don't want that
fate, then pay attention.
We're not the same as that
gang of ass-kissing losers.
We don't indulge in empty
threats or self-coddling
compliments to hide our
feeble shortcomings.
Our breed doesn't need
the aid of such low-brow
extravagances to enhance
our battle performance.
For the moment, we visualize
the death of our enemy.
Their fate is sealed!
They cannot escape the inevitable!
Now then, let's be off,
Pesci, and have some ice.
I recall you saying there was another
soul hiding out in the driver's car,
so let's hurry out there
and finish this mission.
I don't know what kind
of trick they're using,
but if that little harlot
is there, I'll find her.
No, don't worry about Narancia.
That ice is for you.
You're the one who must survive.
Worry about your body temperature.
It's going to take a lot more than a fan
and a damp towel to cool Narancia off.
I know you know that.
The only thing that's going
to help him now is this ice.
At the rate he's aging,
he'll be the first to die.
We're members of the Mafia.
We knew the dangers when
we accepted this mission.
Know that your well-being
outweighs any of ours.
Guarding you is our duty.
Needless to say, you brought
none of this on yourself.
You have my word.
The culprit behind this attack will
meet their end by Meesta's hand.
He'll find a way to pull through.
I know it.
Mista.
They have to be in this car somewhere.
How are they hiding?
Focus.
The key is to start thinking about
the world in four dimensions.
At the binario, Bucciarati picked up
a certain something sent by the boss.
That's it.
If I find that object,
I'll find our quarry.
Hey, Pesci.
You felt another presence
in this car, right?
Have you given any thought
to what it might have been?
Can you still sense it?
I told you everything I know, bro.
It was just weird.
I wish you wouldn't put so much
pressure on me all the time.
I don't have the wits that you do.
Pesci, Pesci, Pesci, Pesci untrue.
I have unwavering faith in your ability,
which is the reason I got
so angry with you earlier.
You need self-confidence.
If you can snap out of this
funk and come into your own,
I know you'll be the unbeatable
force of nature you were meant to be.
What do you say?
That feeling you had
is extremely important.
You need to focus on
unveiling what it meant.
It's your time to shine at last, Pesci.
You must have faith in yourself,
dear brother of mine, and
believe in your amazing power.
I'm amazing?
Yes, of course.
Now think hard and tell me anything
that comes to mind that might help us.
Did something in
particular catch your eye?
Like some strange dark
object, for instance. Huh?
A dark object?
Oh, yeah.
I remember now, big bro.
I was about to look under this
seat here, but I got distracted.
I'm sure I saw something. Huh?
Uh, wow, that's embarrassing.
I guess I was wrong.
I told you, Big Bro.
I knew my intuition was crap.
Why can't I stop being useless?
Actually, I think you're on to something.
Huh?
Do you really mean it?
I'm proud of you, Pesci.
You just solved our mystery.
There's now a light at the
end of this vexing tunnel.
What do you mean?
What light did I find?
Isn't it curious that there'd be random
animal feces under the seat of a train car?
This shit didn't come from a rat.
The thing would be long dead as
their lives are shorter lived than.
Their stool whatever left this
excrement only did so a few moments ago.
You starting to wonder
what all this means? Yeah.
Humans aren't the only species
capable of possessing a stand.
Which leaves only one explanation.
We've got a unique animal
hiding in the shadows.
Mercy kill it. Thankful.
Look!
What the hell is that?
Wait, it's a freaking turtle.
What's it doing here?
Concealing our prize.
Trish, I can see the others, too.
As expected, the boys are passing on
to the big nursing home in the sky.
It's time to strike.
Hope you're ready for another
dose of my aging power.
Thankful death!
Hey, wait a second, big bro.
Look inside.
Aren't they supposed to die?
to have another guy with them huh I think
one of their buddies
pulled a Houdini on us
B-staff!
You have to get up!
Here, take the last hunk of ice!
It'll make you all better!
Maybe it happened because I'm always
expecting things to go sideways.
Or maybe I have my own
guardian angel out there.
But storing ice in my hat was the best
decision I ever made. Number five,
I don't even want to think
about where I'd be right now if
your razor-sharp instincts hadn't
turned back the hands of time.
Your quick thinking totally
saved my ass, little buddy.
The way you stopped the momentum of all
three of those bullets you should be proud.
Number five I have one
more favor to ask of you
if you're about to say
one of us should go to.
Number six has already
been revived and is on
his way he's got the ice
from your pocket and he's
Gonna tell everyone about
the two users who are
closing in on the turtles
so you ain't gotta worry.
I couldn't ask for anything more.
You should save that ice for the others.
Don't think that I'll
be needing it anymore.
Take care of everyone.
I figured out which one
of them's missing, bro!
It's Bucciarati!
He's our missing goon!
Forget Bucciarati!
All that matters is us
retrieving the girl.
Alive!
Get to work! Thankful death!
He's attacking from above!
Your instincts are impressive, and I have
to say you're pretty light on your feet.
The man dressed in black.
Once I off him, the others will recover.
You got it, Bucciarati!
You get rid of this Soul bastard,
everyone will be as good as new! What?
Why the hell is Mista stand here?
I emptied my freakin' gun into
his skull at Point Blake Range!
That should've been all she wrote for him!
So how could that thing
have gotten ice in here?
Whatever you do, don't let it touch you!
Direct contact with the stand
will make you age even faster!
Get him!
Shit!
He's too quick!
Hey, brother!
Eyes on the prize!
Focus on taking care of the
fools hiding in the turtle!
Would you hurry up and do it?
Put these weevils out of commission!
I admit you caught me
by surprise, Bucciarati.
To think that Miesta would go through
all that trouble to tip you off.
Knocking off foes and protecting the
girl regardless of the human cost?
That is the mission the
boss gave you, correct?
You failed your Family.
Die!
The hell?
I will fulfill my mission.
And save my Family.
If the only thing that's
standing in my way is you.
Well then, victory's already well in hand.
It's got speed.
It's much faster than I was expecting.
What did you call it?
Oh, yeah, Zipper Man, I think it was.
The name suits it nicely.
There's no question that you are
naturally endowed with the gift of speed.
But the sad fact of the matter is,
you still don't know the first
thing about using it, Bucciarati.
I guess it's sort of obvious but
I'm a little short of breath.
And from where I'm sitting the same
goes for you that tends to happen
you know when one uses their Stand at
full bore really how foolish of you
clearly that hadn't entered your mind
when you Were ordering your zipper
man to attack me at its maximum speed
and due to your lapse in judgment?
and your rapid aging has resumed.
Someone should have informed you of
this, but the greater the horsepower,
the hotter the engine.
Us two are burning a
whole lot of calories.
Since you seem to be a man
of moderate intelligence,
I'm sure you can take my meaning.
What do you think is gonna happen
as your body heats up further?
No!
Uchirati!
Shit!
The ice isn't working anymore.
What am I gonna do now?
So, what's your next move, huh?
The zipper you put on
me is starting to close.
Soon enough, I'll be right as rain.
And look at that.
There goes the one on my chin, too.
What's the matter?
You feeling a bit stiff and tuckered out?
And this, Zipper Man!
Really, you're so predictable.
Take a dirt nap, Bucciarati!
Once I'm done, you and your friends
will be off to the crematorium.
But don't worry, we'll make sure
the girl is well taken care of.
Would you stop talking?
I knew exactly what
would happen to my body.
Huh?
I was also well aware
that I could be captured.
But a mission must be completed.
And I'll protect my crew.
Kapos worth their salt
must be prepared for both.
That is the burden we all carry.
Can you say the same?
Because I'm raring to go. What?
What?
You can't mean...
You're crazy!
There's no way!
Both of my goals are really quite doable.
As long as I get you off
this speeding train, that is.
Killing you will break the aging
spell, thereby reviving my crew.
Trish isn't going anywhere!
You're a damn fool!
If you want to die, do it alone!
We're going over 150 an hour!
Ironic, isn't it?
You're the one who grabbed
me, if you'll recall.
No!
I refuse to die like this!
It's Jacksonville!
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
Freaking you is all I need.
I need your body.
I want you to make out my time.
I want you to make it.
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Tell me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
I'm freaking.
Thank you.